Gan Hong Wei

Frontend Developer

(60)183103425 • hongwei9703@gmail.com • Klang, Selangor

PROFILE

I'm a Frontend Developer and UI/UX Designer with a passion for creating intuitive and engaging digital experiences. I have experience with HTML, SASS/ SCSS, ReactJS, JavaScript and have a strong understanding of responsive web design and cross browser compatibility. I'm constantly learning and staying up-to-date on the latest web development technologies and frameworks.

EXPERIENCE

EasyStore

2021 - current

Frontend Developer

- Maintain company website using Blade php, HTML, SASS, Tailwind CSS, Javascript and Jquery
- Designed, developed and published over 30 e-commerce themes used by hundreds of business merchants and clients
- Developed customized promotion web pages and landing pages
- Designed and developed UI for new features using Figma & XD
- Experienced with support tickets resolving bugs and website theme customization request

Bluecrystal Solution

2019 - 2021

Junior Software Developer

- Developed and deployed fully responsive websites using ReactJs
- Developed Android/ iOS mobile application and published to both Google Playstore and App Store
- Designed UI/UX for Web projects and Mobile Application and also translate design into functional website.
- Involved in FindMeProp (real estate agent's project), AA13 (mobile application using Unity, C#, php), Bajaku (eCommerce website) and a few other projects.
- Languages used are Java, ReactJS, React Native, HTML, CSS, MySQL. Design software used are Adobe XD and Adobe Photoshop

Ennovation

Web Developer Intern

Jan 2018 - Mar 2018

- Produced web design according to client's requirement
- Involved in web designing, programming and testing phase.
- · Developed troubleshooting skills and design skills.

EDUCATION

University of West of England

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science

Upper Second-Class Honours

Taylor's University

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science

CGPA 3.5+